* [English](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/)Show the language selection submenu.

[](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/ "Travel South Dakota:Home")Toggle Menu

* Things to Do

* Places to Go

* Plan Your Trip

* The Great 8
    
    * [
        
        Mount Rushmore](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/mount-rushmore)
    * [
        
        Badlands](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/badlands-1)
    * [
        
        Crazy Horse](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/crazy-horse)
    * [
        
        Custer State Park](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/custer-state-park)
    * [
        
        Historic Deadwood](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/deadwood)
    * [
        
        Jewel Cave](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/jewel-cave)
    * [
        
        Wind Cave](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/wind-cave)
    * [
        
        Missouri River](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/explore-with-us/great-8/missouri-river)

* [English](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/)Show the language selection submenu.

[Free Guide](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/request-free-vacation-guide)Search

Close Search

Search

Privacy Policy
==============

As stated in the [State of South Dakota’s Privacy Policy](https://www.sd.gov/cs?id=kb_article_view&sysparm_article=KB0010220&sys_kb_id=36d91b371b49c51062c8a8eae54bcb9f&spa=1), the privacy, confidence, and trust of individuals who visit [TravelSouthDakota.com](http://travelsouthdakota.com/) is important to us and any personal information collected on [TravelSouthDakota.com](http://travelsouthdakota.com/) is strictly voluntary. Personal information like an individual's name, address, email address, or phone number is only sought when one requests travel publications, signs up for our **Travel South Dakota** (South Dakota Department of Tourism) emails, enters a sweepstakes, or voluntarily participates in other promotional activities. We only share that information with **Travel South Dakota** partners who aid us in fulfilling your information requests or, in the case of promotional activities, when one agrees to specific use and terms. 

Automatically upon website visit, we do collect certain information that is anonymous for programs like Google Analytics. This non-personally-identifiable data assists us in understanding how [TravelSouthDakota.com](http://travelsouthdakota.com/) is accessed and used aids in marketing research, and aids in targeted advertising efforts. This information is collected through cookies, pixels, or other non-cookie technologies. Third-party cookies like Google not only assist in website insights, marketing research, or providing more personalized experiences, they are commonly used in the [placement of targeted Interest-Based or Cross-App advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/). This type of advertising placement is based on non-personally-identifiable information or prior online activity stored by third-party cookies, pixels, or non-cookie technologies. These technologies generate an anonymous unique identifier to store information like – but not limited to – date of web session, time, city, device type, gender, and pages viewed ([see how Google uses data when you use partner sites like this one](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)). If one has volunteered identifiable information, some information showing certain engagement metrics with [TravelSouthDakota.com](http://travelsouthdakota.com/), **Travel South Dakota** emails, or **Travel South Dakota** advertising may be stored with that personal information for **Travel South Dakota** and partners who directly assist in our digital efforts. In compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), [TravelSouthDakota.com](http://travelsouthdakota.com/) will not serve cookies, pixels, or non-cookie technologies to Internet-Protocol addresses coming from the European Union. Most web browsers default to accept cookies, pixels and similar technologies, but one can adjust their user settings to delete or block cookies (check your device settings).

To opt-out of targeted Interest-Based or Cross-App advertising by non-affiliated third-party ad technologies or networks, we encourage you to visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer Opt-Out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/). If you have previously volunteered information to us and want to request that data or have it purged, [\[email protected\]](https://www.travelsouthdakota.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we’ll see to your request.

See Map

© Copyright 2024 Travel South Dakota
